Hi everyone! In this video, I'm going to show you how to put yourself on the
front page of the website.
So first of all, go to www.addetwork.com and log in with your username and
password.
So there are actually two ways you can put yourself on the front page and I
will show you both.
And then you can decide which you prefer to do, whichever's easier for you.
But first of all, I'll explain a little bit why we do this.
So if we go here onto Webcom and click on online now.
As you can see, there are a lot of members online.
And to be honest, there's actually normally more because right now it's half or
in the morning in the UK.
So it's not the busiest time, yet there's still almost 200 members on.
But usually there's a lot more than this. It could be up to six pages of girls
online.
And if you just log on and don't position yourself on the front page, you're
likely to be somewhere in the back pages.
And this will mean you get a lot less calls because a lot of the time the
clients don't venture through all the pages.
They just select from the first few lines of people here on the front page.
And all of these girls here have all paid and positioned to be on the front
page just like I'm going to show you now.
And that way they're getting a lot more traffic to their profile.
And I believe it's worth doing.
I personally do it every single time I go online, hour by hour.
But it's entirely up to you. Some girls actually put themselves in free chat
like you can see this member has here.
And that also bumps you up towards the front and that way you don't have to pay
.
So yeah, you can try different methods to see what you prefer, but this is how
you pay for the front page.
Okay, so the first way of doing it is to go on to my details and click edit
profile.
Click here on the webcam tab.
And then here at the bottom you click set up positioning.
Okay, so you only ever want to look at the first column here.
You don't want to try and position yourself for the next few days as we just do
this day by day and hour by hour.
Okay, so as I can see here, it's half four.
So the next hour to be online for the front page will be five a.m.
As we do this hour by hour.
And as you can see, I'm trying to click in these boxes, but I can't because
these hours are already gone.
So all you want to focus on is the next hour.
Now, usually we would do this at five minutes to the hour.
So I wouldn't be doing it half four. I'd be doing it at four fifty five.
Just before it turns five as that way it gives the most accurate reason for how
much it's going to cost.
For example, I could pay a couple of credits now.
But then by the time it gets to five, it would have went up and whatever I paid
, it wouldn't matter because I'm not.
It's not going to be on the front page.
So always do it at five minutes of the hour and we start off by putting in one
credit.
Okay, if the box goes red, it means you're not going to be on the front page.
So don't even bother.
Now we're going to take that out and put two credits in.
Okay, so now the box is an orange.
So that basically means that you may be on the front page, but it's not going
to be at the top.
So once again, I wouldn't even bother.
So we're going to take out two and put in three.
Okay, perfect.
So now it's going green.
If it goes green, that means you will definitely be on the front page and
likely be towards the top of the front page, which is what we want.
And what that free is here, maybe I didn't explain this earlier.
That's credits.
So you're paying free credits per hour to be on the front page from five a.m.
To five fifty nine a.m.
Now, like I said, it is usually worth it because usually you get a lot more
calls than you would if you didn't do this and you'll make
that free credits back straight away.
So only I would do it hour by hour as well.
Even if you know, you know what?
I'm actually going to stay online till seven a.m.
And you know, you put free in here.
I wouldn't do that.
I would just do it until six and then five minutes to six.
Go back onto here and put in whatever many credits you need to then do it on to
seven.
You can set yourself alarms as well.
Five minutes to the hour, I still do this every time because if I don't, I do
forget and it locks out at like one or two minutes to.
So yeah, if you forget, then, you know, you've missed out on that hour.
And a little tip actually is to want to 10 screen is to actually add one or two
credits more or even just half a credit more.
So you can do 3.5 or you can do four and that should guarantee that you are on
the front at the top and this is what we want.
And it's always way of just that extra little half a credit or one credit just
to get you at the top of the page.
And once you're happy with that, you press place bids.
I'm not going to do that now because I'm not going to be on the front page now.
So that's one way of doing it.
And another way, which is the new way, is actually doing it when you're on cam
.
So if you click broadcast now, this is going to take you to the page where you
come on.
Hello everyone.
So let me just start my car and log in.
Okay. Now, as you can see here, it's already telling us about the boost button.
This is basically the same thing as being for the front page as I've just shown
you previously.
If we click here on boost.
So as you can see here, this has given you an idea of what the chances are
about the end on the front page.
If you use 5 credits.
And as you can see, if we go on to two, it will tell you, you know, you've even
got a medium chance.
And if we go to one, you've got a small chance just as I was explaining earlier
.
So you can use this way.
I've been in for the front page or the way I've just shown you the both going
to give the same outcome.
So I would do three and then I would even just go on and do four.
And then you click here, bid to boost.
But again, I would wait until it's five minutes to the hour because.
It might go green on three or four now, but then more girls may pay for the
front page.
And then it might actually go up to five.
So then your four credits that you paid, it might not even get you on there and
you still paid that money.
So it doesn't make any sense to do that.
So this is why we leave it until five minutes to just so we can make sure we
get it right.
And yeah, that is it.
Obviously, I'm not going to press place bids now because I'm not going to be
online.
But yes, use whatever method you like best.
The boot button here is probably easiest because it's already there on the
screen that you're on.
But yes, that's all with that video.
If you need any help or advice, please don't hesitate to message us and I'll
see you on the next video.